...大型晨间秀 现在 你想来参加最新大型互动游戏
...the big fat morning show. Now, you wanna play the brand new big fat game:
大型配对游戏 欢迎致电...
Big fat match game, call us now....
喂
Hello?
谁打来的
Who was that?
没说话就挂了
They hung up without saying.
没说话就挂了?
They hung up without saying?
关你什么事
What you care?
你又没用过这里的电话
You never use the damn phone in here no how.
怎么了 伙计
What's up, baby?
你去把里面的电话线给剪了
I need you to get them phone lines up out that house.
断了电话 为什么
Out of the apartment? Why?
Chantay会问我 为什么自己家里不能装电话
I'm saying, what Chantay gonna say about not having no line in her own place?
好 明白了
All right. Got you.
怎么了 伙计 有麻烦了?
What's up, baby, you got a problem?
- 没事 - 我只是随口说说 哥们
- Good. - I'm just saying though, man...
我们这么搞 有点杞人忧天了 伙计
It seem we just going past careful, man. with all of this, man.
像是在小题大做
Like we bugging out or something.
弄得疑神疑鬼的
You know, like we paranoid and shit.
不 我不想用这个电话 昨天用过了
Naw, I don't wanna use this phone. We used this phone yesterday.
你发那声音干吗 伙计
What you blowing out your mouth for, man?
好像没人要找我麻烦似的 伙计
You act like Ain't nobody out to get me, man.
它妈没人跟我作对似的
I got no motherfucking enemies.
没 伙计
Naw, man.
一切都好
We all right.
火线重案组 第一季 第五集 呼机
The Wire S01E05 The Pager
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"...慢了点 迟了点"  -- Avon Barksdale
好 这事很简单
All right, this gonna be so easy...
东区这帮蠢蛋可不像Avon的手下
Them Eastside chumps, they ain't nothing like Avon's people.
看好了 计划如下
Watch, y'all gonna see.
你们在这里 明白?
All right, now y'all gonna be here, right?
等我一会
Hold up.
喂 伙计
Yo, Boo!
我从这里潜入
I'm gonna slide up through here.
Bailey 你守住巷子
Bailey, you gonna cover the alley.
喂
Yo!
喂 Maurice短(货)了 伙计
Yo, Maurice short, man.
- "短"多少 - 三支
- How short? - Three.
那就让他再"长"几寸
Tell him to grow a couple of inches.
你会去哪里呢
Where you gonna be at?
那里就成了陷阱 哥们
That be the trap right there, homes.
你确定他们会跑进巷子?
You figure they roll through the alley for sure?
伙计 老鼠遇到危险总会往洞里钻
Man, rats always run to holes in times of danger.
在说你吧?
And you him, ain't you?
谁?
Who?
"危险"
Danger.
不 伙计 我只是个做事有谱的黑佬 仅此而已
Naw, man, I'm just a nigger with a plan, that all.
还带着把猎枪
And a shotgun.
当然
For sure.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
不小心走错到另外那条通道了
Got myself lost down the other hallway.
那条路通往卸货月台
That leads to the loading dock.
嗯 这仓库够深的
Yeah, and deep storage.
- 这里就是他们给你们安排的地方? - 嗯
- So, this is where they put you? - mm-uhm.
他们的意思够清楚的
Quite a message they're sending.
- 没错 意思就是... - 眼不见 心不烦
- Yeah, and that message is.... - Out of sight, out of mind.
这话真像个地道的穴居人说的
Spoken like a true troglodyte.
这打废纸可牺牲了不少树木
Whole lot of dead trees behind this nonsense.
这是你们办案的根基 探员
The foundation of your case, Detective.
基础打好了的话 你可以在上面建功立业
You lay it in right, you can build on it.
基础没有打好 所有的一切都将功败垂成
You lay it in wrong, everything on top falls.
- 准备好了吗 - 嗯
- We ready? - mm-uhm.
你们能否庄严起誓并确认 依你所见
Do you solemnly swear and affirm that the affidavit is true...
宣誓书表述真实且准确?
And accurate to the best of your knowledge?
- 我能 - 我能
- I do. - I do.
据法律赋予我的权力 我宣布你们结为夫妇
Then by the power vested in me, I now declare you man and wife.
- 他也已经发誓了吗 - 州检察官?
- Did he swear already? - The state's attorney?
嗯 我明白了
Yeah. I see it.
第二副本封存交给法庭
Second copy is sealed for the court,
警方保存其余部分
And the police get the others.
这东西如何工作
How's this work?
和D'Angelo Barksdale用的频率一样
Same frequency as the one carried by D'Angelo Barksdale.
他收到的传呼 我们也能收到
He gets a page, we get a page.
那么 我们都妥当了?
So, we up now?
名正言顺 你们一切齐备
It's official. You're up.
那就让好戏开场吧
Then let the game begin.
当你亲眼见到明星时 你总是会发现他们要矮很多
Celebrities always seem much smaller when you meet them in person.
喂
Yo!
喂 嘿 喂
Yo! hey, yo!
快看 他来了
Check it out, here he come.
有点不对劲
Something ain't right, yo.
小心 伙计 他有枪
Watch out, man, he got that boom.
他带着枪
He's packing.
他来了
Here he come.
喂 快跑 Omar来了 伙计
Yo, come on, Omar's coming, man!
哦 操!
Oh, shit!
"奶酪落了单"
The cheese stands alone.
出自哼的童谣"山谷里的农夫"最后一句
你怎么知道
How you know?
因为你要是染上的话 我早染上了
'Cause if you could,I'd have been had.
嘿  他说只是口交的话不会得艾滋
Yo, he saying you can't catch the bug just by getting your dick sucked.
蠢蛋
Dumb-ass,
你不插进那洞里怎么会得病 明白吗
You gotta be in some pussy to get it, all right?
伙计 要是怕的话就戴套
Man, wear a coat if you want,
不过没人喜欢吸套子
Don't nobody like sucking on a rubber.
你怎么知道的?
How would you know?
你到底想上谁
Who you trying to fuck anyway?
Arletta Mouzone
Arletta Mouzone.
Treenee的表妹
Treenee's cousin.
操蛋 伙计 那样的话
Damn, man, in that case--
得戴个大套 明白吗
Use a big-ass condom, all right?
最好用个垃圾袋 去它妈的
You need a trash bag. Fuck that.
就算用D'Angelo的鸡巴 我也不上那婊子
I wouldn't run up in that bitch with D'Angelo's dick....
脏死了
It's trifling.
怪不得黑佬来这儿偷我们的货!
Easy to see why niggers come around here stealing our shit!
喂 你知道吗 哥们
Yo, you know what, nigger?
什么
What?
算了
Forget it.
142不是一个现行的交换码
142 isn't a working telephone exchange.
美国市内电话只需播3位交换码加后4码
目前截获六个号码
Six intercepts so far,
有五个是空号
And five aren't working numbers?
记录器出问题了吗
Something wrong with the recorder?
和预计的一样
We're getting what you'd expect,
七位数的电话号码
Seven digits of a telephone number
另有两位数以识别身份
And a two-digit add-on to identify the caller,
就像这里 13
Like here, 13.
McNulty 一号线
McNulty, line one.
- 喂 - 你们刚收到过一个142开头的号码吗?
- Yeah. - Did youjust get a 142 exchange?
嗯 我们也是这个号码
Yeah, that's what we got, too.
- 被耍了 - 好吧 回头说
- That's fucked up. - All right, later.
他在克隆呼机上读出的也是这个号码
He's got the same numbers on the readout of the cloned pagers.
所以问题不在记录器上
So it's not the recorder.
这些混混一定是在用密码掩盖呼叫号码
These mopes are using a code to cover their calls?
嗯
Uh-uhm.
- 真够他妈狡猾的 - 怎么回事?
- That's pretty damn sophisticated. - What is?
传呼信息里的电话号码被他们重新编译
They've coded the telephone numbers in their pager messages.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
每次Barksdale手下的呼机一响
Every time the Barksdale kid's pager goes off...
这机器就能提供我们信息和时间
This machine gives us a message and time.
McNulty带着一个克隆呼机 不过这才是我们能给法庭的证据
McNulty's carrying a cloned pager, but this is what we use in court.
还有笔录器
Same with those pen registers.
每次有人用平房大院里的公用电话
Every time a pay phone in the low-rise court is used...
我们就会收到电话号码
We get the telephone number,
拨打时间以及持续时间
The time and the duration of the call.
还有拨入的电话
Incoming calls, too.
搞间谍啊 真棒
Spy shit. Very cool.
你说他们用了某种密码
You say they're using some kind of code?
嗯 肯定如此 这些号码它妈的毫无意义
Yeah, they got to be. These numbers don't make no fucking sense.
你打的电话?
You rang?
Omar的座驾 Bubbles发现的
Omar's ride. Bubbles spotted it.
和之前不同的牌照 没有被人报过失窃
Different tags, no stolen report,
他们还是用的旧车
These come back right for the van...
不过被Bub认出了车顶行李架
But Bubs makes it by the cargo rack on the roof.
好眼力
Good scope.
你想擒下他吗
You wanna take him?
可以试一下
Can't hurt to try.
我们抓捕Omar 搜出枪
We pop Omar, get a gun,
他也许会配合我们的工作
He might let us work him.
呼机上有什么线索吗
Anything coming through on the pager?
目前收到八次传呼
Eight hits so far,
大部分都带着某种密码
Most of them in some kind of code.
这些不是Baltimore的电话交换码 这点可以肯定
These ain't Baltimore exchanges, that's for sure.
花了三周时间去征得Daniels同意
Three weeks to get Daniels to agree,
一周时间搞定宣誓书 结果换来的是这种狗屁结果
A week to write out the affidavit and then this bullshit.
这种密码能有多复杂
How complex a code can it be
用它们的不过是群蠢蛋
If these knuckleheads are using it?
何况要是我们不能破译 大家要情何以堪?
Then again, what does it say about us if we can't break it?
你要是送Bubs回市区 我就在这里等你
You wanna run Bubs back downtown, I'll sit here and wait for you.
好的
All right.
我错过什么好戏了吗 姐们儿
What'd I miss, girlfriend?
连个狗屁都没有
Not a goddamn thing.
很无聊是吧
Yeah, boring, ain't we?
你们每天这么无聊 难道不会想吸两口解解闷?
How y'all do what you do every day and not wanna get high?
我到挺想知道的
That's what I be asking.
这里有点乱嘛 是吧 小老弟
It's been a little hectic down here, right, cuz?
String 伙计 的确如此
String, man, I can't lie.
那伙持枪打劫的毛贼 让我们落花流水
Them stick-up boys, they caught us dead up.
还有那些缉毒的条子
And the knockos,
操蛋 我不知道是怎么回事
Shit, I don't know what the fuck that was.
5-0 条子来了
5-0. Coming up!
5-0 coming up, y'all.
收摊
Time-out.
拜托 伙计 怎么搞的
C'mon, man, what is that?
什么
What?
你得让你的手下明白
You gotta get your crew to understand
那些打劫的和惹是生非的家伙
That it's the stick-up crews and the creepers...
才是让我们最头疼的人
That give us the most trouble.
等他们也那么想了...
When they start thinking like that...
就不会再有什么"惊喜"了 明白吗
You're not gonna have any more surprises, you feel me?
因为你叔叔和我
'Cause you know, your uncle and me...
认为你店里有个告密者
We think you got a snitch up in the shop.
什么
What?
有人给抢劫佬通风报信
Someone who tips off the stick-up crew.
你会去查的 对吧
And you gotta be on that, right?
你得去查查
You gotta be on that.
我告诉你怎么做
I'm gonna tell you what you do.
今天是周几? 周五?
What day is it today, Friday?
周五有什么事
What happen on Friday?
发薪日
Payday.
- 今天别发钱 - 为什么
- Not this Friday. - Why not?
不 你要做的是假装叫他们过来拿钱
No, what you gonna do is you gonna call 'em Iike you gonna pay 'em
然后让他们空欢喜一场
And then you crack 'em.
告诉他们 你对他们的工作他妈的非常不满意
You tell 'em you're not happy with what they fucking pass as work down here.
当你不满的时候 他们一分钱也拿不到
And when you're not happy, they ain't getting paid.
你明白我的意思吗
You feel me?
明白 但是String 不付钱 没人会帮你做事
Yeah, but String, you don't pay a nigger, he ain't gonna work for you.
你以为他们会去找工作?
What, you think a nigger's gonna get a job?
你以为这帮小兔崽子会说
You think these niggers gonna be like,
"去它妈的 我不干了 我要去读大学?"
"Fuck it. Iet me quit this game here and go to college"?
不可能 他们会抵触一阵
Naw, they gonna buck a little,
但是 他们不会离开
But they not gonna walk.
最后你会获得尊重
And in the end, you gonna get respect.
是的
Yeah.
然后等他们钱花完了
And when that money run out,
他们就会回来巴结你
They'll come up to you and roll on you...
问你提前支点钱什么的
And ask you for an advance and shit,
因为他们一穷二白了
When they flat-ass broke.
这些人你就可以从怀疑名单里划掉
Them the niggers that you strike off your list.
但那个仍旧有吃有喝...
But that nigger that stay eating...
不动声色 不来问你要东要西的家伙
The nigger that steady rolling, ain't asking you for shit...
就是我想知道的那个(内鬼)
That's the nigger I want to hear about.
明白吗
Understand?
明白 伙计
Yeah, man,
你倒挺会把人逼上绝路的 String
Shit, you know how to play a nigger into a corner, String.
嘿 料理一下那个家伙
Yo, take care of this right here.
你是我的最爱
You my favorite girl.
操 我会处理的 伙计
Shit, let me handle this, man.
喂 Poot
Yo, Poot.
- 是啊 我... - 过来 伙计
- Yeah, l-- - Come here, man.
怎么了
What's happening?
它妈的这啥玩意?
What the fuck is that?
它妈的这啥玩意? 不懂规矩吗?!
What the fuck is that? You know the fucking rules.
你它妈的在干嘛?
What the fuck are you doing?
复印
Copying.
一部电话
A telephone.
我受不了这种破小组了
This fucking detail is too much for me.
已经过三点了
It's after 3:00.
那么 那些小子们呢?
So, where are the boys at?
他们可能都是夜猫子吧
Maybe they only come out at night.
我以前有个像Omar那样的线人
I used to have a guy like Omar working for me.
叫Reuben Terry
Guy named Reuben Terry.
他行吗
Is he good?
街头巷尾 轻车熟路
Saw the street like we wish we could.
绝对优秀的线人
Ain't nothing like a good Cl.
放学了
School's out.
能用一下你的电话吗
Can I use your cell phone?
嗯 我买了
Yeah, I got that.
真的
I did.
我知道
I know.
我不知道这次...
I don't know about this....
你不知道? 你这是什么意思?
You don't know-- What do you mean, you don't know?
- 我怎么能再相信你... - 我的老天 Elena
- How can I trust you.... - For chrissakes, Elena,
我是他们的父亲 你觉得我会让他们睡地板吗?
I'm their father. You think I'd let 'em sleep on the floor?
是的 我都买了
Yes, I got them.
床单 枕头 被子 枕套
Sheets, pillows, comforters, pillowcases.
- 我它妈都买了 - 是什么颜色的
- I fucking got them. - What color are they?
颜色 他妈的是什么颜色关你屁事啊
Color, what the fuck do you care what color they are?
喂
Hello?
她挂了
Lost her.
- 我猜也是 - 你明白吗
- I bet. - You know something?
我前妻 有时候她的行为
My ex-wife, the way she acts sometimes,
她处理事情的方式
The way she deals with shit...
会让你觉得 如果是一个比我野蛮的人
You would think a less enlightened man than myself,
一个比我粗俗 更不解风情的人
Cruder man than myself a man less sensitized
不在乎什么女人味啊 魅力啊 价值啊
To the qualities and charms and value of women...
那样的男人 不是我 但那样的男人
A man like that, not me, but a man like that,
也许会叫她一声婊子
He just might call her a cunt.
你刚才是叫你孩子的妈婊子吗
You just called the mother of your children a cunt.
不 我没这么叫她
No, I did not call her that.
- 是的 你当然叫了 - 没 我没叫
- Yes, you fucking did. - No, I did not.
我们先别吵了 行吗 我有事要做
Let's just leave this, okay? I got some stuff to do.
条子来了 快跑
5-0, gotta go.
哦 伙计 闪开
Whoa, man, get out the way!
- 操蛋 - 这次到挺老实的
- Shit. - Not much fighting this time.
没力气了吗 蠢货
You getting tired, asshole?
Kima揍得他还没缓过神来吧
Still dragging from the whupping Kima put on him.
作为警察 没放半点水 对吧
Fucked you up like a cop should, didn't she?
那可是Kima的一个优点
That's one thing about Kima,
她能像男人一样叫你好看
She put a hurting on you like a man.
他妈的给我起来
Get your monkey ass up.
你想拿回你的名片 是吧
You're gonna want your business card back, right?
走吧
Come on.
* From Bantry Bay to the Derry Quay *
* And from Galway to Dublin town *
* Well, I've never seen *
* My brown Colleen *
* That I met in the County Down *
* There's a man in the County Down *
我先进去 扮白脸
First, I go in, play nice.
然后你进去 扮黑脸
Then you come in, play bad.
我可是来真的
I ain't gonna be playing.
手铐太紧了吗
Bracelet too tight?
你可是劣迹斑斑啊 是吗
You racking up all kinds of points, ain't you?
先是把一名警察送进了医院
First, you put a cop in the hospital,
那一拳几乎要了他的命
Damn near kill his ass with that punch.
现在又从"男孩村"(少管所的名字)里逃出来
Now, you on the wing from Boys' Village.
伙计 我才十六岁
Man, I'm 16, all right?
他们他妈的能拿我怎样
What the fuck they gonna do to me?
那可是你最不该担心的 我的朋友
That's the least of your worries, my friend.
我有个同伴正等在外面 迫不及待想进来修理你一顿
I got a partner outside who can't wait to get in here and fuck you up.
被你打伤的警察 是Herc的老舅
Cop you banged was Herc's uncle.
Herc这回可是谁都拦不下了
Herc wants off the leash on this one.
我猜你是现在还拦着他的人?
And I suppose you at the other end of that leash?
听着
See,
我不想那么做
I don't want to play it that way.
我知道你这一路走来不容易
I know about coming up hard and all.
为什么 你也是苦过来的吗
Why, you came up hard?
东边 Flag House公房区
Flag House projects. Eastside.
嗯 Flag House?
Yeah, Flag House?
你让我想起我自己
You know, you remind me of me.
我想...
I'm thinking...
我们还是把事情结了算了
We should work something out.
我能得到什么
What do I get?
你想要什么
What you want?
我想...
I want...
让你舔我的鸡巴
For you to suck my dick.
看我不他妈的揍死你
I'll beat your fucking monkey ass.
你可是来扮白脸的 傻逼
You supposed to be the good cop, dumb motherfucker.
什么
What?
您好 能为您效劳吗
Hello, may I help you?
我们想找个位子
Yeah, we'd like a table.
你们有预定过吗
And you have reservations?
没有
Naw,
我以为 你知道 我们进来就有...
I thought, you know, we could just walk in....
让我查查
Let me see what I got.
两个人?
That's two?
请跟我来
Follow me, please.
您的大衣 女士
Your coat, ma'am?
我们能坐那边那桌吗
Can we get that one, over there?
今天是周五 那些位子是留给预定过的老主顾
It's Friday night those are for patrons who made reservations.
我来帮您 女士
Let me get your chair for you, ma'am.
- 我不用了 伙计 - 请拿好菜单
- It's okay, man, all right. - Here you are.
给您菜单 先生
Here you are, sir.
服务生很快会过来
Your waiter will be with you shortly.
你应该对他强势点 Dee
You shoulda pushed him, Dee.
该死的
Bastards.
警官
Sarge,
少教所的电话一直没人接
Nobody answers at juvenile intake and we been calling.
显然 他们没你们两位探员那么敬业
Clearly, they're not as dedicated as you two detectives.
那收容所当班的什么时候能来
So what time does the duty intake consultant get here?
你们错过了八点档
You missed the 8:00.
下一个大概半夜里来
You got another one around midnight.
半夜?
Midnight?
如果我们把文件留下
You think maybe if we left you the paperwork,
你能在收容所的来之前把他关起来吗
You could put him in the box 'til intake gets here?
烦人
Hemorrhoid.
是给您清理面包屑
For the crumbs.
好吧
Yeah, right.
- 晚饭还喜欢吧 - 当然
- You like your dinner? - Yeah.
虾肉非常不错
That shrimp was right.
- 是啊 很棒 - 嗯
- Yeah, it was good, right? - mm-uhm.
你觉得他们知道吗
Think they know?
知道什么
Do they know what?
你知道 我的工作
You know. What I'm about.
你是什么意思 Dee
What you mean, Dee?
拜托 你知道的 就像...
Come on, you know, it's like...
我们精心打扮 对吧
We get all dressed up, right?
穿过市区 大老远跑到这个高档饭店
Come all the way across town. Fancy place like this.
吃完饭之后 我们会再去港口边
After we finished, we gonna go down to the harbor.
散一会儿步 是吧
Walk around a little bit, you know?
好像我们就生活在这里 你明白吗
Acting like we belong down here, know what I'm saying?
那又怎样?
So?
你有钱 不是吗
Your money good, right?
Dee 我们不是这里唯一的黑人
Dee, we ain't the only black people in here.
我不是这个意思 我是说我们来自...
It ain't what I'm talking about. It's about where we...
拜托 你明白我的意思
Come on, you know.
我是说 你知道
I'm just saying, you know,
我觉得身上有些烙印挥之不去
I feel like some shit just stay with you...
你知道我的意思 就算你再怎么努力
You know what I'm saying, like, hard as you try...
还是原地踏步 你明白吗
You still can't go nowhere, you know what I'm saying?
请问需要甜点吗
Can I interest you in dessert?
是的 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
- 来份巧克力蛋糕 - 我把车推来
- Can I have some chocolate cake? - I'll bring the cart.
小子 没人在意你和你的那些破事
Boy, don't nobody give a damn about you and your story.
你有钱 把自己说得天花乱坠都行
You got money, you get to be whatever you say you are.
就是这样
That's the way it is.
哦 先生 抱歉 这些是样品
Oh, Sir, I'm sorry. These are the samples.
先生您需要什么
And for you, sir?
好的
Very good.
别装B了 承认吧
Don't be a bitch, admit it.
来吧
Go ahead.
认错吧 做个男人
Admit you're wrong, be a man.
是啊 我得承认...
Yeah, I gotta confess...
这个三明治比那个狗屁Bob家的正点很多
This sub beats chink-ass Bob's by a mile.
也许你揍起人来身手不错
'Course, you might be all that when it comes to thumping on niggers...
但你的杆法也太臭了 伙计
But you can't do shit with that stick, man.
你打得更好?
You'd do better.
我会打
I play.
他说他也会打
Says he plays.
或许吧
He might.
我用两只手打得更好
I'm even better with two hands.
我查过了 伙计 Stinkum说得没错
I checked it out, man. Stinkum true on this one.
除了那个从纽约来的黑佬 Scar
Except for that nigger, Scar, from New York...
Edmondson街无人入主
Edmondson gully is wide open.
Tee-Tee那帮人呢?
What about Tee-Tee's crew?
他们被联邦调查局抄了之后 就销声匿迹了
Naw, them niggers dried up when they took that federal charge.
大多数人都躲了起来 吞云吐雾
Most of 'em laid up somewhere, getting high and shit.
听我说
I'll tell you what.
你去跟那Scar打个招呼
You holler at the boy Scar.
让他知道 是时候滚蛋了
Let him know, man, it's time for him to take a stroll.
如果他敢不从 让Wee-Bey和Bird去摆平
If he give you any beef at all, we'll put Wee-Bey and Bird on it.
好的
All right.
一旦我们把他赶出那里
And then once we got him outta there...
我们就派马仔进去 赶走那些当地的白痴
We'll send in the smokers to run out all the little poop-butt locals and shit.
或者 如果你觉得其中还有些可造之材
Or, if you think there's some cats in there who got game...
- 那就把他们招进来 - 好的
- then we put 'em on our team. - All right,
你想派谁去管?
Who you want to run it?
- 让Stinkum去吧 - 好的
- Send Stinkum up here. - All right.
他发现了发财的地方
He the one who saw the shot.
这个机会就给他吧
So, he gets a shot.
好吧 好吧 打的不错
All right, okay, not bad.
这可不能让值班警员看到了
Can't let the duty officer see that.
你想歇会吗 伙计 你都输了60了
You wanna give it a rest, man? You down $60.
那也许是你一天的薪水 但对我来说几分钟就赚回来了
That might be your whole damn salary, but I clock that shit in minutes.
摆球 继续打
Rack 'em and break 'em, man.
你们在等收容所的人?
You the guys waiting for juvenile intake?
他在集合厅
He's in the squad room.
如果还有时间 我会打败你的
If I had more time, I'd run you.
给你点建议 Preston
Give you a tip, Preston.
你要是还想挣黑钱
You gonna run a hustle,
最好别说漏了嘴
You best stay with what you know.
伙计 去你妈的狗屁建议 好吧
Man, fuck you and your tired-ass advice, all right?
不过...那个三明治还真不错
But that sandwich was good.
你把我们的生意带去Edmondson街
You gonna move our little thing down to Edmondson Avenue.
拿下那块地盘
Take the gully.
那Scar呢
What about Scar?
谁
Who?
听着
Listen,
我给你卖货的提成
I'm giving you points on the package...
所以好好干 听到了吗?
So, you make a go of it, you hear me?
你也在给自己干了
You working for yourself, too,
搞些好的货色出来
So you gonna put out the strong product...
让当地贩子望尘莫及
And you gonna get the locals behind it.
就这么简单
It's as simple as that.
带好你的人马 明白吗
You get your team together, you feel me?
现在下楼等我吧 我很快下来 伙计
Go and wait for me downstairs. I'll be down in a minute, man.
我们马上带着钱上路
We gonna make this money run in a few.
高兴点 哥们
Smile or something, nigger.
今晚可让他威风了
Made that nigger's night.
是啊 不过这是他应得的
Yeah, he deserved it, though. He deserved it.
是Wee-Bey 我们逮到一个了
It's Wee-Bey. We got one.
你觉得是Omar吗
You think it's Omar?
不 我觉得是那些年轻人中的一个
Nah. It's one of the young 'uns, I think.
- 一个倒下了 还有两个 是吗 - 是啊 那伙狗娘养的
- One down, two to go, right? - Yeah, motherfuckers.
还想抢我
Try to rob me, baby.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
找到了
A winner.
有匹配的结果? 哪个案子?
A match? Which case?
你刚刚拿给我的那个 Bunk
The one you just brought me, Bunk.
那个东北区姑娘枪击案里的弹壳
Casing in that girl shot up in Northeast.
- Kresson? - Diedre Kresson 没错
- Kresson? - Diedre Kresson, right, yeah.
和去年的两个案子里的都相符
She matches up with two other cases, both from last year.
- 哪两个? - Toreen Boyle
- Which ones? - Toreen Boyle....
还有个叫Ligget的什么混蛋 报告里有
Someone named Ligget. It's in the report.
是Toreen Boyd和Roland Leggett
It's Toreen Boyd, Roland Leggett.
没错 就是他们
Yeah, them.
这三起案件的凶器都是点45口径的
Casings from all three killings go to a .45,
可能是柯尔特经典款左轮手枪
Probably Colt Classic.
柯尔特 - "左轮手枪之父"
该死的Landsman 怎么让他发现的
That fucker Landsman. How's he do it?
这三宗案子让你喜欢上了Landsman?
You like Landsman for these three?
我不知道 Bunk
I don't know, Bunk.
作为一个上士 Jay就是个无良的人
As sergeants go, Jay's a sociopath and all,
但其实我不得不和一个真正的流氓为伍
But I'd have to go with an actual gangster.
Jimmy 你是坐着吗
Jimmy, you sitting down?
那很烫 但如果你戴上了烧烤手套
I said it was hot, but ifyou got these barbecue gloves.
- 这里有叫Johnny Weeks的吗 - 谁
- You got a Johnny Weeks up in here? - Who?
- Johnny Weeks - 在游戏间
- Johnny Weeks. - Over in the game room.
- 谢谢 - 有烟吗
- Obliged. - Any smokes?
我戒了
I'm out.
你在这里多久了
How long have you been here?
你得给药一点时间 让它们在你身体里起作用 伙计
You gotta give the medication a chance to work in your system, man.
给你带了些东西
Brought you something.
几块炸鸡和些薯条
Yeah, some chicken pieces and some fries.
本来还有杯奶昔 但我在公车上打翻了
Bought you a shake, but I dropped it on the bus.
袋子里来 袋子里去
It comes in a bag, goes out in a bag.
尿袋:因尿道梗阻而在膀胱处造瘘 引尿至体外
用那东西多久了
How long you have that for?
我惨透了 伙计
I fucked up, man.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I saw.
我无能为力 你明白吗
There was nothing I could do, you know?
我先是被人揍了 然后又得吃这药
It's like first I got beat, right, then I get this.
这些药有什么用
What are these for?
他们说我"中招"了
They say I got the bug.
"中招"?(艾滋病)
The bug?
我住院的时候 他们检查过了
They checked me when I was in the hospital--
他们确定吗
Are they sure?
你去哪里了
Where you been at?
到处转悠 我在努力
Here and there, I'm at it.
我应该早点过来 但我有个任务
I'd have come past sooner, but I been on kinda like a mission.
- 任务? - 是啊
- A mission? - Yeah.
那些打伤你的毒贩现在可有麻烦了
Them hoppers that beat you down they got problems now.
他们...甚至他们卖命的人
Them and the people they sling for, even.
什么
What?
我让条子盯上了他们
I put the police on their ass.
- 条子? - 是啊
- Police? - yeah.
- 你是被关起来了还是怎样 - 没有 拜托
- What, you get locked up or something? - No, come on.
我不是为他们卖命 是配合他们工作
No, I'm not working for them. I'm working with them.
虽然他们不会给我警徽 但我还是会这么干
They don't give me the badge soon enough, I keep doing like I do.
为什么
Why?
什么为什么
What do you mean why?
你怎么能问我为什么
How can you ask me why?
为什么你会待在这里 伙计 和这些苟延残喘的傻逼们
Why the fuck are you in here, man, with all these falling-down motherfuckers?
为什么你尿尿还得用个袋子
Why you passing shit through a bag?
为什么他们要打伤你
Why they beat you down?
为什么我无能为力
Why I couldn't do nothing about it?
这些都是游戏的一部分 不是吗
It's all part of the game, right?
我是说 这是你教我的
I mean, you taught me that.
你在这里过得怎么样 伙计
What you up to in here, man?
参加聚会
Doing the meetings.
戒毒会?
N.A.?
嗯 一天两次
Yeah. Twice a day.
很好 伙计
That's good, man.
很不错 能让身体好起来 知道吧
It's good. you give the body comfort, you know.
是啊
Yeah.
不 你需要改变
No, you needed a change.
我也这么觉得
Guess so.
这个月底我就出院了
I'll be getting out of here the end of the month.
没关系 戒毒会哪里都有办
It's all right. They got meetings everywhere.
你不用担心
You ain't gotta worry about that.
Bubs
Bubs.
现在谁手上的货最好
Who's got the best package now?
- 别说这个了 伙计 - 我要回家了 不是吗
- Get the fuck out of here, man. - I'm coming home, right?
你瞧 现在哪有什么好货
Shit is weak all over, you know?
不过在Baker和Calhoun街来了一批人
Got some boys up in Baker and Calhoun, though.
虽然之后就赶走了一个毒贩子
They had a smoker out the other day though.
- 是吗 - 打趴下了几个黑佬
- Yeah? - Knocked a couple of niggers out.
看看你这一路走的
Ain't you a trip?
被打趴下了 带上了尿袋 还想着出去抢劫毒贩子?
Beat down, bagged up, still ready to rip and run, huh?
我可是个"北欧海盗" 伙计
I'm a Viking, homes.
"我可是个北欧海盗 伙计"
"I'm a Viking, homes."
McNulty
McNulty.
这里有东西需要你亲亲
There's something here that needs kissing.
是啊 再说一遍 你这口臭的家伙
Yeah, Speak again, toothless one.
我猜你现在知道为什么我是带杠的了吧?
I guess you know now why I wear the stripes in the family.
干得漂亮 Jay
Good call, Jay.
当然 如果Keeley没有遗漏现场...
Of course, if Keeley hadn't fucked the scene up...
你几个月前就能拿到那枚弹壳了吧?
You'd have had that casing months ago, right?
Keeley 你就随Keeley去吧
Keeley. Let Keeley be Keeley.
这个城市里每个人都是不完美的 不是吗
We all can't be princes of the city, now can we?
说到这儿...
Speaking of which...
坐下
Sit down.
我能问一个与你职业息息相关的问题吗
May I ask you a question that is essential to your career?
什么
What?
你为谁工作
Who do you serve?
我是在认真的请你说出谁是你长官
I am asking you to identify for the record your commanding officer.
- Rawls警长 - 很好
- Major Rawls. - Excellent.
带着这个想法
And with that thought in mind,
我建议你立即去警长办公室
I advise you to go immediately into the Major's office...
带上我给你的Kresson案件的突破发现
Carrying the break I've given you in the Kresson case...
去拍他马屁 因为...
And kiss the man's ring. Because...
我刚刚说服他 让你跳出了屎坑
I have talked you right out of the shithouse.
是吗
Yeah?
是这样的
Here's the deal.
你和缉毒科两周内把这案子搞定
You wrap up this thing with Narcotics in two weeks.
你就可以回来执勤做夜班了
You put yourself back in the rotation when we go back to night work.
你做到了 就能归队
You do that and you're back in the fold.
谢了 Jay
Thanks, Jay.
不客气
No problem.
这不对
Shit ain't right.
做事才能拿钱
You work, you get paid.
我就是这意思
That's what I'm saying.
我会去和他谈谈 好吗
I'm gonna say something to him, all right?
- 你该这么做 - 说得没错
- You should. - Truth.
- 你好 Dee - 你好 美女
- What's up, Dee? - What's up, Shorty?
530刀 数目没错
$530, the count is right, man.
好的
Okay,
补给正送过来
Re-ups on the way down.
去告诉Sterling 做好准备
Go tell Sterling to be ready for it.
好的 等等 Dee
All right. Yo, Dee, man.
你知道 我和Poot 我们努力的干到现在 你知道
You know, me and Poot, we been steady working it, you know?
没马虎过 没出乱子 对吧
Nothing sloppy, no troubles, right?
没错
No.
我们在想
And we was wondering if,
你能否先借我们点小钱
Maybe you could let a little something go...
在发薪日前 因为你知道 现在
Until payday, 'cause you know, right now,
我们只是些穷光蛋
We some broke-ass niggers, man.
此刻 对那女孩下毒手的人
Right now, whoever did our girl...
一个月前也杀死了Boyd和Leggett
Also did Boyd and Leggett a month earlier.
- Leggett - 而那两个案子...
- Leggett. - And those two are definitely...
绝对和涉毒争斗有关
Straight-up drug executions.
两件案子里都没提到Dee
No mention of Dee in either file.
但我搞到个新号码
But I did get a fresh number...
Tywanda的
On Tywanda.
谁
Who?
Kresson案打电话报警那个
The girl who called in on Kresson.
- 对 - Dee是她说出来的
- Right. - She put Dee in for that.
你见过这个吗
Have you seen this?
嘿 "傻蛋"(Jaybird正好带了个Jay)
Jaybird.
然后那只熊说
And the bear said,
"你不是来这打猎的 是吧"
"You didn't really come here to hunt now, did you?"
你周六出警了?
You see Saturday's 24s?
周日早上
Sunday morning.
你有看到Worden在西区接的案子吗?
Did you see the one Worden got on the Westside?
John Bailey(Omar的同党) 穿了件防弹背心
John Bailey, in a Kevlar vest,
遭三名枪手袭击
Lit up by three separate shooters.
在Carey街
Carey Street.
你窜联了Kresson的案子
You made the Kresson connection...
怎么没把Bailey和Barksdale联系起来呢?
You didn't think Bailey might tie in with Barksdale?
Worden是另一个队里的(夜班组)
Worden's on the other shift.
我只是尽力查清自己的案子 我的老天
I'm trying to work my murders, Jesus Christ.
Tony 三号线
Tony, Line 3.
你们怎么查了那么久?
What took you so long?
你可能听说了 Baltimore出了几件命案
You might've heard, we get a few murders here in Baltimore...
有时候我们要回顾一下
Sometimes we just get backed up.
- 没人跟着你们吧 - 为什么会有人跟着我们
- You weren't followed here? - Why would we be followed?
Diedre曾和些可怕的人来往
Diedre was playing with scary people.
你是指谁
Who might that be?
谋杀案发生后 你报了警 告诉探员...
You called this in after the murder and you told the detective...
说你在她被杀的那晚和她聊过
That you talked to her the night she was killed.
是她打来的
She called.
已经很晚了 她没说上几句
It was late. She didn't talk long,
她说她得挂了
She said she had to go.
Dee在门口等她
Dee was at the door.
这是你最后一次和她说话吗
And that was the last time you spoke with her?
是的 她是那晚遇害的
Yeah, she was killed that night.
Dee是她男友吗
Dee was her boyfriend?
不是 Dee好像是他男朋友的侄子
No, Dee was his nephew or something.
Dee大概是D'Angelo Barksdale
Dee would be D'Angelo Barksdale.
她男友是叫Avon Barksdale吗
And the boyfriend, Avon Barksdale?
你知道Avon?
You know Avon?
问题是 你是怎么认识他的
The question is how do you know him?
你也在街头跟那帮混混一起混过吗
You out there running the street with the players?
我以前是...
I used to be...
但Diedre出事后就没有过了 我是说 该死的
But not after this thing with Diedre. I mean, damn.
我们以前会去Odell夜店的女士之夜派对
We used to go to Odell's for ladies' nights...
有一次他在那里
And one time he was there
带着朋友在一个大包厢里点喝的
With all his people in one of the big booths ordering drinks,
摆出一付国王的派头
Acting like he was king of everything.
Diedre上钩了
And Diedre ate that shit up.
你呢
And you?
说实话
I ain't gonna lie.
我以前有段时间也沉迷夜店 但是...
I did the club thing for a while, but...
那些个地方 都会有人在玩些游戏
Some of those places, everybody in there's on some kind of game.
但是Diedre和Avon搭上了?
But Diedre went with Avon?
她和Avon在一起有一年了...
She was with Avon for like a year...
然后出了点事
And something happened.
到最后 她开始变得充满占有欲
Toward the end, she started getting real possessive
让Avon很不习惯 因为他身边还有其他女孩
And that didn't sit with Avon,'cause he has other girls, too.
她一会儿牢骚满腹
She started bitching on him one minute...
一会儿哭天喊地 威胁说她什么事都做得出来
Crying the next minute, threatening to do all kinds of things.
她威胁了Avon Barksdale?
She threatened Avon Barksdale?
那女孩发飙了
The girl was off the hook.
有一次 她威胁要写信告发他
One time, she threatened to write a letter on him.
一份信?
A letter.
写给州检察官
A letter to the state's attorney.
好像是她的亲戚
Supposed to be some sort of kin to her.
她说如果他甩了她
She said that if he dumped her...
她会去告发毒品的事
She was gonna tell about the drugs.
她后来写信了吗
Did she write this letter?
我不知道
I don't know.
我试着和她聊过她的所作所为
I tried talking to her about the way she was acting,
但她就是无法释怀
But she wouldn't let it go.
有天晚上她甚至在他的夜店和他大吵一架
She even had it out with him in his club one night
- 当着所有人的面 - 什么 Avon有个夜店?
- in front of all the people. - What, Avon has a club?
Orlando's 脱衣舞酒吧
Orlando's, titty bar.
是他开的吗
Does he own it?
Diedre是这么说的
That's what Diedre said.
她说他名下的生意不计其数
She said he owned a whole mess of stuff.
跟我说说 伙计
Tell me something, man.
什么
What's that?
你管这地方 怎么就没精尽人亡?
How can you run this place and not just OD on pussy?
操蛋
Shit.
你试试打理这些婊子和她们的破事几天
You try dealing with all these bitches and their problems for a few days.
你就会情愿去开个自助洗衣店
Get so you'd rather be running a goddamn laundromat out this fucker.
听说你把Pit经营得不错
Heard you're doing okay in the Pit.
嗯 还行
Yeah, well.
怎么 你不觉得吗?
What, you ain't getting it like that?
伙计 我老舅还只发我工资
Man, my uncle still got me working on salary.
该死的 小子
Damn, boy.
你不是你老舅盯紧的人
You ain't the only one your uncle keeps close.
什么
What?
拜托 伙计 你还嫌不够?
Come on, man, you ain't making no ends?
我知道你目前为止赚得不少
I know you getting something on this by now.
不 伙计
No, man.
我只是个幌子
I'm just the front,
去酒管局申请执照需要一个没有案底的人 我是说...
Clean name for the liquor board. I'm saying--
什么意思
What the fuck?
你有意见吗
Is there a problem?
你付的是前一杯
That was for the drink before.
我付的是这杯
It was for this one.
我并不是要对你老舅说三道四
It ain't like I'm calling your uncle out or nothing...
但要给兄弟个机会 "蛋糕"该人人有份
But give a nigger a chance. Plenty of pie out there for everybody.
同意
Believe.
你听说了Stinkum要"加班"了吗
You heard Stinkum gonna be coming off the clock, right?
能拿提成了
Getting a percentage.
什么
What?
开辟一块新领地
Open up fresh territory.
接手Edmondson和Brice的街角
Take over the corners down near Edmondson and Brice.
我老舅把那块地方给了Stink?
So, my uncle gave that to Stink?
我还以为你知道
Figured you knew.
Orlando
Orlando!
我说 Orlando 你能过来帮个忙吗
Excuse me, Orlando, can you help me down here, please?
我已经付过这杯的钱了
I already paid for that last drink.
你付的是前一杯
That was for the drink before.
- 操 是这杯的钱 - 出什么事情了
- Hell, no, that was for this one. - What's up here?
听着 他不肯付酒钱 我就少收了20刀
Look, he ain't paid for that drink and I took $20 off the bar.
她拿了20刀 然后又再要20刀
Look she took $20, then $20 more.
我就它妈拿了
Hell I did.
拜托 为什么你要这么对我
Come on, now, why you gonna do me like this?
我在这里坐了一个半小时 一直请你喝酒
I been with you for an hour and a half buying drinks.
听着 伙计 这不是坑人吗
Look, man, this ain't right.
我刚刚花了120刀请你喝酒 给了40刀小费
I just spent $1 20 in drinks, $40 in tips.
现在到了这个地步 你还想黑我的钱吗
Now, you gonna take all that and still try to sneak into my pocket?
操 婊子
Shit, girl!
你得走了 把他撵出去
You got to go, get him the fuck outta here.
我不过就是摸了摸你的膝盖
I ain't done so much as touch your kneecap.
我试着尊重她
Trying to treat her with a little respect,
而这就是你回应我的方式?
And this is the way you do me?
慢着 慢着
Wait, wait!
你为什么那么做
Why you do that?
你拿了他的钱吗
Did you take his money?
不 我没拿过他的钱
No, I didn't take his money.
你请我喝酒?
You buying me a drink?
我能见见你吗
Can I see you sometime?
我是指 在其它地方
Like, you know, not in here.
我通常不和在这里搭上的男人约会
I don't usually see men that I meet in here.
通常
Usually.
什么样的脱衣舞店会在门口装摄像头?
What kind of strip joint has a video camera looking out?
比起姑娘们 也许更为了自己的店着想
More to it than the girls, maybe.
那么 他拥有夜店 他拥有仓库
So, he's got the club, he's got the warehouse...
他在Druid Hill湖边有幢公寓
He's got the apartment building by Druid Hill Lake...
他还有家拖车公司
He's got the tow truck company...
这还只是她听来的 他向死者吹嘘的部分
And that's just what she knew from what he bragged about to the dead girl.
警长喜欢资产
Major likes assets.
我猜副局也是
The Deputy, too, I imagine.
没什么比没收财产更能增加部门预算了
Nothing like a few property forfeitures to swell the departmental operation budget.
查查市府档案 看看谁是夜店的老板
Check city assessments to see who owns the club.
去工商局查查公司名
Run the company name through the state corporate charter office.
而且 凶案科在星期六接了起案子
Also, Homicide picked up one Saturday night.
可能也是我们在查的
Might be one of ours.
John Bailey是持枪抢劫的老手 我曾在Murphy听说过他
John Bailey, he's a stick-up artist I used to know from the Murphy homes.
他当时穿着防弹背心 不过没用
He was wearing Kevlar, but it didn't help.
现场留下了39个弹壳 来自三把不同的枪
39 casings on the scene, from three different guns.
为包纸袋(毒品)就下这么狠的手
Overkill for a burn bag...
不过要是他和Omar是一伙的 那也能解释
But about right if he was running with Omar.
看 目标出现
Look it, our buddy.
我真希望他们能用个正确的号码 哪怕一次也好
Just once, I wish they'd use the right number.
我不喜欢他迟到
Ain't like him to be late.
Bailey 这个操蛋瘾君子
Bailey, you fucking dope fiend.
我告诉你
I'm telling you...
那些傻逼靠不住
Them fucking people ain't to be relied on.
为什么你总是满嘴脏话 伙计
Why you always gotta talk like that, man?
- 什么 - 操这个 操那个
- What? - "F" this and "f" that.
如果我不说它
If I give it up,
我话里的意思就要少一半
I lose half of what I mean to say.
没人想听脏话 伙计
Don't nobody want to hear them dirty words, man.
特别是从这么漂亮的一张嘴里说出来
Especially coming from such a beautiful mouth.
要等Bailey来吗
Wait for Bailey?
早起的鸟儿有虫吃 伙计
Early bird catches the worm, dog.
我呼过你
I beeped you.
我没收到
I didn't get it.
让我瞧瞧
Let me see.
你想看我的呼机?
You want to see my pager?
嗯
Yeah.
你当真 Prez 想看我的呼机
Sure, Prez, you want to see my pager?
我也呼过你
I beeped you too.
你没事吧 Prez
You all right, Prez?
714-3432
714-3432?
我收到过 那是你打来的吗
I got that. That was you?
你试过回电吗
You try it?
试过两次
Yeah, I tried it. Twice.
是空号
Non-working number.
如果你知道密码就能打通了
It would've worked if you knew the code.
操 我和你一样吃惊
Shit, I'm as surprised as you.
我喜欢猜字谜
I like word-search puzzles.
明白吗 就是找出隐藏的单词
You know, where you gotta find the hidden words?
于是 我觉得
So, I thought
我也可以在那些数字上下下功夫
I could do the same thing with the numbers.
以我发你的那个号码为例
Take the number I sent you.
现在 把7跳过5
Now, take the seven and jump it over the five.
会得到3
You get three.
把1跳过5
Jump the one over the five...
会得到9
You get nine.
4对应6
With four you get six.
3对应7 4对应6
Three, that's seven, four is six...
再来是3对应7
A three again...
然后2对应8
And two is eight.
0对应5
Zero switches with the five.
所以714-3432对应的是
So 714-3432 is...
396-7678
396-7678.
这里的电话
Our number.
- 这就是密码 - 没错
- And that's the code? - yeah.
这招靠谱 因为这只要看那些数字键的位置
And it works, because it's all about where the buttons are on a phone.
如果密码中包含了数学...
If it was a code that involved math...
代数 或是其它含义
Or algebra or whatever...
那些公房区里的小混混怎么搞得清楚呢
These little yos in the projects wouldn't be able to follow along.
但如果用这招 你所做的只需跳过按键5
But with this, all you gotta do is jump the five button.
与数学无关 只要...
Ain't no math to it. It's just...
看着拨号的键盘就行
How a phone looks when you look at it.
Prez 你真是个天才
Prez, you little genius!
- 老天 我该宰了你 - 太棒了
- Jesus. - I could kill you, that's so good.
你老妈一直吵着要我把他接出来(Maryland州康复中心)
Your mother keep ragging at me to take him outta here
送到私人疗养院里
And put him in a private nursing home.
是啊
Yeah, well,
你知道 她始终无法释怀
You know, she ain't never gonna let that go.
我一直告诉她 伙计
I keep telling her, man,
我们还不能用到这笔正当的钱
We can't show this legit money yet, man...
特别是他还没有医保
Especially since he ain't got no insurance.
不过很快就能用了
Soon, though.
嗯
Yeah.
你来这里的时候还小吧?
So, you ain't big on coming here, right?
是的
No.
听我说 伙计
Tell you something, man...
你快见到你老舅了 明白吗
You about to see your uncle, you understand me?
他是我们的家人
This is family.
我明白
I know.
家庭很重要 家庭才是全部
Family is what counts, family is what it's about.
家人总在身旁 因为血脉相连
Family gonna always be there,'cause it's blood.
伙计
Man.
你从来没想到过这个 对吧?
You never figured on this, did you?
活出生命 引领人生 没什么大不了的
Live the life, lead the life. Ain't no big thing.
他以前常说那些狗屁东西 自己也深信不疑
He used to talk that shit all the time and he believed it,
你明白我的意思吗
You know what I'm saying?
怎么了 伙计 现在再说呀
What's up, baby, talk that shit now.
你知道 你是对的
You know, you're right.
待在这里确实有点痛苦
It's kind of hard to be in here right now.
他吓到你了 对吗
He scare you, don't he?
我的意思是...
You know, I'm just saying--
他让我害怕
He scares me.
没错
Yeah.
瞧 如果他死了 我会好过些
See, if he dead, you know, I could carry it better.
想到我们已经经历的  你倒真有点希望那样
Coming up the way we did, you kind of expect that.
等着那个时刻
Waiting on it.
瞧...
See...
其实 你只能完蛋一次
The thing is, you only got to fuck up once.
慢了点 迟了点
Be a little slow, be a little late.
就那么一次
Just once.
但是人总有迟钝的时候
And how you ain't gonna never be slow...
总有晚的时候
Never be late?
你没法规划它 伙计
You can't plan for no shit like this, man.
这就是人生
It's life.
是啊
Yeah.
吓到我了
Scares me.
他们还在用这辆车
They're still using it.
周六晚上我来过 没见着它
I was by on Saturday night and it was gone.
下班时间吗
On your own time?
你还接你儿子吗
You still getting your boys?
嗯 今晚去我家睡
Yeah, tonight for a sleep-over.
Omar行动了
Omar's rolling.
搞什么
What the hell?
要请求支援吗
Call for backup?
时候未到
Not yet.
看看他在玩什么花样
Let's see how it plays out.
一个邀请
An invitation.
这么偏僻也找不到支援了吧
Feel a little lonesome for backup.
是啊 我也这么觉得
Yeah, me, too.
好极了
That's nice.
我去检查车子后面
I'll check the rear.
我盯着他们
I'll watch the boys.
午安啊 先生们
Afternoon, gentlemen.
我说 你要是需要开枪 你早开了
Saying, if you were gonna use that you would've been done using it by now.
车子没问题
It's clean.
你得保持干净
Got to keep it clean.
这可是我们的赌本之一
We having one of our little parlays like this,
总得保持干净吧
Got to keep it clean, right?
Omar上街不带枪?
Omar with no gun on the street?
应该是头一遭吧
Must be a first.
是啊 有时候顶着张脸就够了 伙计
Yeah, sometimes who you are is enough, dog.
但是看你们盯我的车这么久
But being as y'all sitting on my ride so long,
我想还是帮你们省点时间吧
I thought I'd save y'all some time.
有话直说吧
Come straight on out.
我可不接受任何指控
I ain't taking no charge.
你没办法把我扔回监狱
You ain't putting me back in no cage.
我们不是来抓你的 Omar
We're not here to bury you, Omar.
我们是来找你合作 因为我们有同样的麻烦
We're pulling you up 'cause we got a problem in common.
麻烦?
Problem?
Barksdale
Barksdale.
他可不是个麻烦
No, he ain't no problem.
我不清楚
I don't know.
Avon做了不少人...
Avon's been chalking up a lot of bodies.
而你又我行我素...
And you being you....
照你这么说 我到觉得他有点麻烦 但是...
Put it that way, I guess he could be a little problem, but...
我真的没法出面帮你们
I just can't really come out and help you all.
你明白我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
我讨厌告密
Snitching just rubs me wrong.
我觉得游戏不是这么玩的
Personally, I don't think the game is played like that.
我们尊重你的选择
We respect that.
如果你碰巧受到指控
If you do happen to take a charge though...
我是McNulty 她是Greggs
I'm McNulty, that's Greggs.
你打给我们 我们会帮你想办法
You give us a call, we'll sort something out.
很公平
Fair enough.
你知道吗 我曾在收容所工作
You know, I used to work the homes,
那时你哥还在那里
Back when your brother was up there.
你有机会...
You get a chance...
告诉他 昨晚他们杀了John Bailey
Iet him know they blew up John Bailey last night.
他是个好人
Good man.
树敌太多
Lot of enemies.
嗯
Mm-uhm.
我说 你们在抓Bird吗
Saying, you trying to catch up with Bird?
听说他杀了一个工人
Word is he dropped a working man.
等等 慢着
Wait, hold up.
拜托 别耍我
Come on, don't play me.
什么工人 谁是Bird
What working man, what Bird?
拜托 工人还能有谁 是吧
Come on, now, ain't but one working man, now, is there?
Bird呢
And Bird?
你的线人心里清楚
I think your snitch can handle that.
操蛋 Bubbles知道Bird
Shit, Bubbles know Bird.
你在加班?
You working late?
- 就一会儿 - 有空吗
- A little. - Got a minute?
当然 请坐
Sure, have a seat.
不用了 站着说比较好
No, this is better said standing up.
你知道 我工作13年来从不受重用
You know, I've been 13 years on the shelf.
我不是在抱怨
I ain't bitched.
这是我自己的选择
It was me that put me there.
但我现在来了
But I'm here now,
我得说点心里话
And I gotta say a piece.
我们该对公房区的公用电话实施窃听
We should've had a tap on the project pay phones by now.
那里的线报能让我们查获毒品
A wire there will get us the drugs.
盯得紧点 我们也会嗅到钱的味道
Keep pushing, we'll get a whiff of the money, too.
我知道你很在意升迁
I know you're serious about climbing that career ladder
我也知道爬得越高越容易掉下来
And I know how slippery it gets the higher you go...
但就我而言
But for me...
我这次是孤注一掷了
I don't want to go to no dance unless I can rub some tit.
我欣赏你的坦诚
I appreciate your honesty.
晚安 副队
Good night, Lieutenant.
你说什么了让Dee付了钱
So, what you say to make Dee pay out?
我告诉他要么给钱 要么吃我一顿老拳
I told him to give it up or I'm taking him out of the count.
- 操 - 听着
- Shit. - Look.
必要时 我也会揍人
I'll pump niggers when I got to.
- 是他! - 谁
- That's him. - That's who?
抢劫我们的人中的一个 那个浅色皮肤的小子
One of the ones that robbed us. That light-skinned boy.
是他吗
That's him?
好 我们走
All right, come on.
我是它的头号玩家
I'm the king of this shit.
- 那么你的意思是让我们等着 - 是的
- So, you want us to wait? - Yeah.
- 好 我们盯着 伙计 - 好
- All right, we on it, man. - All right.
那个人就是Scar
There goes Scar right there.
那个穿蓝衣服的80号?
Right there in the blue? Number 80?
好 我盯着他
Yeah, I'm on him.
好 你认准他了吧
All right, you got him?
- 快去找个公用电话 - 出什么事了
- Find a phone real quick. - What's wrong?
我的兄弟Dee好像有急事
It looks like my man Dee got himself an emergency.
怎么 他又招摇了?
What, he been stuck up again?
怎么了 你要什么
What's up, what do you need?
我手下在Greek的店里发现了Omar的人
My people are onto one of Omar's boys down at Greek's.
确定?
Word?
好 别轻举妄动 我会去处理的
All right, sit tight. I'm gonna take care of it.
好
All right.
没人过来
Ain't nobody coming.
Dee说等着
Dee said wait.
我没说错吧
Told you.
他还在里面吗
He still in there?
嗯 他在打游戏
Yeah, he's playing the games.
好的
All right.
你挺机灵的 孩子 叫什么名字
You are sharp, son. What's your name?
- Wallace - Wallace 好
- Wallace. - Wallace, all right.
这个小兄弟会给我们指认 明白吗
This nigger's gonna point him out to us, all right?
喂
Yeah.
搞定了 干得漂亮 小老弟
It's done. Nice work, cuz.
好的
All right.
接收时间:20:42:33  通话时间:7秒